yes y'all this is the Amanda seals show
I am Amanda seals and it's time for
another edition of I
[Applause]
KN so I did an interview on Club
Shay and I still I don't know like how I
feel about it I have a lot of feelings
about it because I sat back and watched
it
and um as I was watching it I can see
why people don't like me but I don't
have any desire to change those things
about me uh but I can see I could see it
like I'm just so deliberate when I speak
I'm so deliberate and I'm so
unwavering and I can see why folks would
hear that and hear a sternness in it
like a rigidity in it that feels like
someone being
scolded um so like I talk like a cop but
I also talk like a teacher that wants
you to learn you know like I talk like a
parent but then I also talk like a coach
that really cares about you winning the
game and it ends up being perspective on
how you receive that and you know while
I was watching it I had to do my own
work to not let the negative thoughts
that are always kind of just fluttering
around in my head waiting to get you
know caught on to I had to really let
that go and and and lean into the the
uniqueness of like what I just describe
like the different perspectives uh
because I think if all of us step back
and watch ourselves we will have
critiques about ourselves it's
fascinating though because majority of
the people who who would ever critique
me like they've never been interviewed
and had to watch themselves right or
they've never even yeah that's a fact
that's a fact they've never been in a
situation where they had to be
questioned and then now like go back you
know what I mean like often times like
people may be questioned even in an
insular space right like you're
questioned by people that you know but
it's private um and I think that there's
just such a different experience when
it's happening public and I'm fearless
about it but it doesn't change like my
feelings about it so it ends up feeling
a little bit bit conflicted but
nonetheless I just want to thank anybody
who felt like they got something
positive out the interview and and felt
the need to share it with me um it was a
fascinating
um it was fascinating watching myself
deal with someone coming at me yeah
that's got to be a different experience
yeah yeah like I watched myself get
untense you know like I like I watched
myself go from intense to
untense um but you know it's funny the
person I'm talking to was like you're
ready to get canceled again
[Music]
tomorrow I can't wait to watch I'll hit
you back I was
like so you know nonetheless um the
moral of the story here for the IB
knowing though
is be kind with yourself and be gentle
with yourself at the same time as being
honest with yourself and sometimes it
feels like those two things cannot exist
in the same space but you know it's it's
really at the end of the day only you
that you can control and you really
can't control anybody else and un
unfortunately you just can't control
their experiences you can't control
their perception all you can really do
is try your best and uh one of the
things that was fascinating while I was
watching it was I was watching my
autism okay and it was things
that I didn't like I talk really fast
and like when I like you'll see like
pockets of the interview where I'm like
really intensely talking about something
I'm really
into and it's like oh and there's like a
word for it I'm still learning these
things but like there's a word for this
and it's like I'm being castigated in
the chat for this oh she just talk too
much she just be she just be talk
dumping on people you know like talk
dump you know and that's the new word
for me talk dumping you know um then I
would see you know myself trying to just
like defend myself even when I shouldn't
have to right like I'm I'm seeing like
things about me
um being just like questioned that I
didn't think deserve to be questioned
but nonetheless it was it was really
just interesting to just experience that
as an outsider with this recent di
diagnosis which some people have said
like it's not a good idea to speak about
your diagnosis well I mean it's not a
good idea for me to be Pro prop
Palestinian either but here we are so um
you know I think everything is relative
but that's another addition of I be
know we up we up we up man show